<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Gatsby Starter Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[A starter blog demonstrating what Gatsby can do.]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 14:49:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[ILYMUN 2019]]></title><description><![CDATA[2019 will be the seventh consecutive year in which the International School of Lyon and the Cité Scolaire Internationale de Lyon collaborate…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/about/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;2019 will be the seventh consecutive year in which the International School of Lyon and the Cité Scolaire Internationale de Lyon collaborate, to organize ILYMUN. The conference will take place In mid-January, (dates to be confirmed in September), in the prestigious Hôtel de Région Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes (1 Esplanade François Mitterrand, 69269 Lyon, Cedex 02). We invite keen and bright high school pupils to join us to debate and take action!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2015 the UN adopted 17 goals, the Sustainable Development Goals, and set targets for 2030. The theme of our conference, Inequalities: Bridging the Gaps, addresses Goal 10. In defining this goal, the UN explains that “Inequalities based on income, sex, age, disability, sexual orientation, race, class, ethnicity, religion and opportunity continue to persist across the world.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have seen that economic growth is not enough to reduce these disparities. The gaps between the rich and the poor are growing bigger. In addition, it is clear that inequality is a serious threat to social and political stability as well as to the environment and sustained growth. Thus, inequalities within and among countries is one of our biggest challenges. In the same report, the UN gives us courage in stating that “Inequality is not a matter of fate or chance and can be reversed through policies and reforms.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that by involving youth in finding solutions and taking action, we can make a difference. Therefore, in addition to our core MUN committees, we will once again host the Action Assembly, in which students represent themselves rather than countries in order to work towards real change in their local communities, and the Youth Conference for “collège” or middle school students from the Auvergne- Rhône-Alpes region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will also offer the Model International Court of Justice (ICJ), a forum that mediates conflicts between two nations by reflecting on treaties, international conventions, and international law. The ICJ is a unique and enriching experience for delegates who wish to try something different to ordinary committees, particularly for those interested in pursuing a career in law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, we guarantee ILYMUN 2019 will be, an unforgettable experience!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;History&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking inspiration from FERMUN in Geneva and THIMUN in the Hague, two students from the Cité Scolaire Internationale, Pierre Mohamed and Kaelan Tardy, reached out to students at the International School of Lyon in order to organize the first ILYMUN conference in 2013. Most of the schools participating in that first conference are now regular participants in our annual conferences and many have gone on to model their MUN clubs and even their own conferences on ILYMUN. We’re delighted to see these developments as it means more communities working together to change the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Our Values&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;1. Enriching Education&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that the main aim of MUN conferences is to educate the participants, providing them with essential skills such as public speaking, collaboration with others and critical thinking. MUN opens one’s mind and encourages in-depth reflections on our complex world. ILYMUN helps students grow and become global citizens. Here is a quote from one of our friends at INOMUN in Lille that captures our view of MUN: “The aim of debating is to resolve problems with words, without violence, without deaths. We, high school students, are the next generation. We have to act, we have to do something. A MUN won’t literally change things, but it is a way to sharpen our critical mind and our intelligence in order to take over our parents’ generation. In order to bring peace.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;2. Constant Innovation&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you may have noticed, ILYMUN has matured since its inception by the virtue of original projects we develop every year. Of course, the central issue of the conference varies from year to year, with new branches and new committees created to bring diversification and an improved experience. Undeniably, the criticism from you, fellow participants, permits us to improve an important number of aspects of the conference, making it finer each year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;3. Human Experience&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most diplomats tell you that the most efficient decisions, those which actually change the world, are taken in convivial moments after a day of debate. This is wholly legitimate. Therefore, we keep in mind that an MUN conference is an incredible place to meet new friends. A few essential factors, unique to ILYMUN, allow you to have real exchanges: small committees (from 20 to 100 persons) country delegations made up of different schools, housing with host families and, of course, social events!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;4. By Students, For Students&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though a very small team of adults supervises our agenda and the organization of ILYMUN, every aspect of our conference — the vision, the planning and the execution — is done by high school students who are doing their best to provide middle school and high school delegates and their MUN directors the best possible MUN experience and a professional conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;5. Social and Ecological Engagements&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bearing in mind the ILYMUN 2016 conference resolutions to tackle Climate Change, we take concrete action to save the Planet, by respecting environmental values. We use a minimal amount of paper and transfer to digital as frequently as possible. We strive to be role models for a green conference.&lt;br/&gt;
The past several years we also have committed to debating the work and the value of various NGOs in our General Assemblies. Delegates then make a vote that leads to real action. The NGO that wins the majority vote receives a financial donation from ILYMUN. This donation is made possible by the wonderful support of our sponsors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;6. Sponsorship&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To make ILYMUN truly outstanding, we rely on generous sponsorship from institutions as well as private companies and individuals. We are currently sponsored by the Région Auvergne Rhône-Alpes. Last year we were supported by Boehringer Ingelheim, Media 6, Riso, Heidi Heras MD and inter-nations, amongst others. By financially helping ILYMUN, you will be effectively helping us reach our goals of providing a professional conference and encouraging young people to work towards positive changes in our world. For more information, click here to view our sponsor’s brochure (in PDF format). If you or your company are interested, our Public Relations Team is here to answer all of the questions you might have. Contact: tom.badou@csianglo.org&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Action Assembly]]></title><description><![CDATA[A unique committee where your voice is heard! What is Action Assembly ? In the Action Assembly, delegates do not represent a country, but…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/action-assembly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/action-assembly/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A unique committee where your voice is heard!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What is Action Assembly ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In the Action Assembly, delegates do not represent a country, but rather represent themselves. Delegates work together to develop “action plans” in order to make real change in their own communities, in their regions, in their countries and even on a global scale. Their action plans offer the ILYMUN community a direction or vision as well as real-life opportunities to make change.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What’s this year’s theme ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This year, the Action Assembly will work towards the reduction of inequalities on a local and global scale by working closely with NGOs specializing on this subject. This will broaden the debate and provide delegates with the tools they need to complete their mission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What are we going to do ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Over the course of the three days, there will be guest speakers from various NGOs in order to share their experience and knowledge on reducing inequalities and to guide us in developing our action plans for change. There will also be lobbying and discussion time in which the delegates will &lt;strong&gt;create projects&lt;/strong&gt; that could be put in place, and &lt;strong&gt;develop a charter of 19 acts and/or pledges&lt;/strong&gt;. The charter will be posted on the ILYMUN website as both a vision and concrete steps we can all take towards reducing inequalities.&lt;br&gt;
At the end of the conference, the members of Action Assembly will present their projects that students can implement and they will present the charter of actions and pledges that will show the ILYMUN participants how they CAN work to reduce inequality.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;How do we prepare for the Action Assembly ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will be posting research reports regarding various NGOs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We also encourage delegates to research these and other UN posts about Development Goal 10, reducing inequalities:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.uua.org/sites/live-new.uua.org/files/sdg_10_reduce_inequality.pdf&quot;&gt;UUA Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.unwomen.org/en/news/in-focus/women-and-the-sdgs/sdg-10-reduced-inequalities&quot;&gt;UNWomen Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/partnership/browse/&quot;&gt;UN Browse Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/partnerships/actionnetworks&quot;&gt;UN ActionNetwork Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finally, we encourage delegates to research and identify an NGO THEY would like to work with to tackle this year’s issue. Delegates should be prepared to present this NGO to the Action Assembly and explain what projects students could get involved in with this NGO.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Why should YOU join the Action Assembly ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is the committee where your own voice is heard. This is the committee that actually works towards real change. It’s a great mix between the formal debating of MUN conferences and informal discussions. It’s the committee where you’ll collaborate with people to develop real plans and concrete actions in order to change things in your own community. If we all make small changes in our communities, we can change the world! So, don’t hesitate anymore and join us in the Action Assembly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Committees & Issues Debated]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ilymun 2019 General Assembly The Respect of the Fundamental Rights endowed to all by the charter of the United Nations Security Council The…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/committees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/committees/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Ilymun 2019&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1qkUgtF8VtI-1rtgB1ZAuAVdSUOHjYUrFGgHNi0uC324/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The Respect of the Fundamental Rights endowed to all by the charter of the United Nations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1JXxAY4CA24UUkkP_GXeS0xmZeEOyUQis8b0RZzABVFI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The issue of the Rohingya people&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Bk0rYlO2twnUMtdF4O-LP50TsrBkdgufrcv7KnGXTNI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Working towards a unified Bosnia Herzegovina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/18hupxkrwzHScvhqzwxk6pJdrg2ELnQgUEOkJOt5GL60/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The right of nations to have nuclear arms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Historical Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/15jSnRJdVmLW6Q8G2gXQFsNLZLSbSuR24yyJyMUlvWyA/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The recognition of the state of Israel and its membership in the UN; May 1948&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/103B3qeFI_Cpgl5duP-LEMJUmqqx-asGS-ME7fEEZVfw/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Drafting the Nuclear Non Proliferation Treaty; August 25, 1967&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1QWu3Mve1AM5KwXo44uzsrLrHTZXMFOL647kCM5ReBVg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Rwandan genocide; April 30, 1994&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Territorial&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1vx2_SiD5jDIl4q8egVI6O8CQevIKeovu?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Sharing global resources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This committee will work towards the creation of multiple resolutions regarding specific resources (water, minerals, forests, oil, etc.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Environmental&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1U8cf6xz2wrHoDLiY8RCxvKtesgxBw9eI53Ca6z-z_78/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The pollution “market”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FqmpqxPqeKCTYneaEkjQO2JwNzcrBfn3UKF3yaVv1uI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Sustainable development: a balance between economic growth and the protection of natural resources and ecosystems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Economic&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1LemTIRZi04H3lZ_wmLfVXPOHycZmEOtQj_7mRtiz_N4/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Equality in the workplace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1V_1XyON8PeQRiLjGuj6oF7g5cxVBwQnL6e0n2Cvu_NI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Reducing poverty as a step towards equity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Social&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1gB_iBYlp2Y94Hb7GCLz-xiD0EapQeOuoBcQJowRXry4/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Reducing discrimination&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1NppMAPJd3eL2EJZyIi_hrcJGylNP4mGPMQYF4ygaaL0/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Universal healthcare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Human Rights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/15cjGASjC7M3KYvXZpdfN7TuideWbrrqNoFstYLZ1e8g/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Police brutality and discrimination of minorities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1aeWUQiIxcmpIqkjvQdKMje5wDA689QazK14q_IgEbpE/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The protection and the rights of migrants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Conference: Focus on Children&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1WxAz5GyxWxopmVKHk4CrSZDzGBMgnxGYxg-wehL_H9o/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Healthcare and mortality rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1F_TauSK7R69Atw3TLb9eVE7h92Uw2wafzVdDrK5ZDqU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Protecting the rights of the child&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1tZDIYwpEVeVViKR7CUm9tT2pMXNng1h0p3GK8jj1YvM/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Action Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1vv7VzZJn6NxrkroLLDJklqCBCoMpU9lI/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Gender inequalities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1gKMtw16cSMB8GVLk4zcqFfpEr0VeDzwT/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Unequal access to culture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/14HGBEwQ27aglY0XsY0taXj-CVV_4mZc8/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Unequal access to health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Conference: Focus on Women&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/12yJnfdllyckCDxFvDEvetgzuKSxD6KZcpe5Tzgo5NuQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Reducing gender inequalities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1xmQUWaLW3abFrF_4Oe7sA0oCTSbe8elKDFYeTKuYBuc/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Empowering women&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2018&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;ilymun2018&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;card card-body&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1mZMZYBlwidT05QvGHQ9xlfu0ekoi9rk6zjsPJEv4Uyg&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Securing cities against acts of terrorism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WfCUn79gEK1wfHmG1iDHeQaTSsYIH2L8S5ot35Eyvtw&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection of civilians in civilian war zones, Aleppo, Syria&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1G21BI9YQUw3X0Wzb3CU1ZHbwXZthTG8pHpem6GYvEf4&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question of Chechnya, Russia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1Hvv0HmaHtO5PgfuZctBPu9WvQX3wCZ3GvYiumvQ70fQ&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Securing cities against acts of terrorism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WfCUn79gEK1wfHmG1iDHeQaTSsYIH2L8S5ot35Eyvtw&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Historical Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Korean War: June 25th 1950&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1ofAMq6jOINqo5MDwylQlruItBGY1i1JaagcZC7vIzy8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cambodia: 30th April 1977&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=15gfOuBJU6axa2A5978mhCZvjUJ9gW9P7cDwLs58J9Ws&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cultural&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approaches to preserving cultural heritage within urban areas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1yQVM_FBsfvqMmsU4ztByieBj1uoU2qSZ0S8jADA8-1k/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protecting UNESCO historical cities from ravages of war and siege&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1iOE6PqVWBeYm6bvlaMxOqTPltoLvGguDPOrr4Ur5vJ0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Development&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The issue of informal settlement in rapidly developing urban areas in LEDCs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=15vGmQnWv0Vhcv8KOztD0ux42-YId_QUiADNYeYn-5M0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The implementation of the goals of Agenda21 in urban areas of LEDCs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1ONzB7-WWQ1mkQf7vn63qCMDF_hxJ48XSqPRoSXeRXl4&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;ECOSOC&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting the demands of an ageing population in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1chez1NA9OfuKeifwQvAplvj1tMU8qBnE23NZvlBfdCc&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Problems faced by megacities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=14zZ5vGypUp7YCgsPJy4EJO2tYHmDOrbUM4zXtzHWsk8&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Environmental&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Measures supporting cleaner and greener cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=12ZaZ0-wPsHgWUwj5i-PGyW5r8z-eqR2sAuhRyFcDGfE&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Climate change and disaster risk in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1ftJKk7jDNfgueYvPC96v_tIQq4wZegQ4U9htpbzG8n0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Science and Technology&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The use of renewable energy sources in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WcB2lZiM8ni9MdoGWdgwhny7rNA3NgJEiqYeu8t33L8&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question of smart cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WbKnKi6XCHrhC7rC0Xjy-d9VuHVqdr_Ca1US3FKAjy0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Human Rights Conference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protecting the rights of refugees in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1_CcCkOBmwn4yufRlR7562WnY-r_K5IQCp0UnBSMD4Dg&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Providing equal access to basic services&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1IW8y1Juw0iq0f1TJWIBqsUtejFS4F1PL5COOCFjgVPg&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;International Court of Justice&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;War crimes in Aleppo, Syria&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1sl5eCsLmO3_NCGIemvTk-T2U-H5hXLd4&quot;&gt;Click here to access related documents&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Action Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Integration of marginalised people&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1NBnTTprGfyHc6d5KFvxza-CZ4r1NkitEOELSjdo5nnQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Integration of young migrants in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=12qfnMMEA1NnHMBmipwSDE90fj6SOMRc8GMBM_Q7fqQ0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cities studied:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1okaRCumLKkeNyRZ3nWfLZcVGWRiiEl2zfN9Z0IXB1Oo&quot;&gt;Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1QgSdg_L12vo-wz9M2rEJskW8mcZHR6cCblHMt2oMBJw&quot;&gt;Mumbai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1YoxL2mqNX6s9I4AmWEjr5snIj0O4Lv2DX_dqnJeDElQ&quot;&gt;Nairobi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=15GFPaeEvgWaLs-1zRL_Eh8oz9aXs31xCUgVYa5eM6pY&quot;&gt;Paris&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1wmM2UqYtYNEqzEjyeOsGGrm_EjcyvUc89CkYlTB2s8Q&quot;&gt;Tehran&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/a/csianglo.org/document/d/1FrMZtA-JTyhmuWY7r1KR9aQkanWa624tayZhtzNhDXU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2017&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;ilymun2017&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;card card-body&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1JpfiHrOpacGmjmENI21GCwWCWs_TIxGUhWpqf2FvjyE/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technological governance and democracy &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fFy1aYFiNdMknKTYWEMKZAm0wf1vN6b7U-9lSfw9pLo/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cyber warfare &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1L-ddWxrcGid-6M8u50kyifalEp0q1ZEMk7OQPSnGWGw/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Issue of security vs. privacy &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1SATkNofvVAD0ya_kvjteKJhl_UCql-Mr3Oj0z-xhzAA/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting heritage sites from armed conflicts &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1PYhItq2k8Ivk7c3NCOxN7Yfsuj9QrB0hKBnIt_-Mvf8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cultural Memory&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mass media’s effect on culture &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/194KxwpDGT188KWo9nR35hHJlZPpZDKOrXBpi05NKE9E/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting heritage sites for and from tourism &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CutMrkE8Ir6P8Mi9PDb_NkTMMR7c0_yBFykZNKZuzb0/edit?pli=1&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Claims to historical artifacts and documents &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1gSQQLI_spdai3CQcy5QREEGCg4xKb1qPzKi4pnvGrOY/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Resource Management&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The issue of the “brain drain” &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1SoEDeW2_gExktLlmlgySDUVmzkuLXHVi-0oNq8x1MN8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing food distribution &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Mzok1oXPNmea4IHnLun3Hk5dSGD99KvxTjHm137FWcg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing ocean resources &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fruxIZRd14gTQyColguNlt9aEH0xh8MXHc8_9hPoDTQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EcoSoc&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reducing technological disparities to promote economic equality &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FOu9K0sf-mR-DK_rQx7XmQ7co-W8YzBSTabXa0qlUSQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Economic power of technology &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1cPK5M5lQ8nJxrpiy2PYax2vRjjngl1CE4dB81SRQslM/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fighting poverty and inequality in a globalized society &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1wJTKM2eaxAqzEtsRXiDmbQcUSpSZUNYyyRPgvzROYLA/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cultural Identity&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting and promoting indigenous cultures &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Oy7pXLwl4EBTnj1Sl1sflq4IC4UxifncOZXVOOYa3qk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining cultural identity in a globalized world &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FDbZI44kTnZ0yblKXa6UhrZs6GXeb1-9lM6ZxtzTNKk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting human diversity in the face of biotechnology &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1pmF2MVwCxDRyFrpJHsnv4Ab-vXxhgMzeOBdzRRKRghg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Migration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fighting human trafficking and providing safe migration &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/11ebC2Xr67S4895I1hNRLwUOETtefDb9s9dnwroBFJ4w/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rights of refugees &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B0a_hZsHRAFFbWhqa1JxdUNjUF9maTNTdWFZWWFKUEVZVzRF/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The role of borders and freedom of movement &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1V6BbkQoi9qlu8Lhjff8N9kVgfo36j5NZnBrcVt8Oh0M/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Human Rights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promoting gender equality &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1g-_PCbeJv_IA15Pate7STp8G8oApiZAu-koj4aeWQvM/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liberty of thought and expression &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/14ZZb2OLROlVcw6a-91BSRn57speIPU0XXb5EStqZ2Lg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promoting self-determination &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/11NUHdUJe4QTtWpOfK4X1c64AvQr1K9bjX6Vt2m0wSBU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Science and Technology&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication, technology, and extremism &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/14XEiC-S6xIkpkyWDJmOT7IXcxgZm1AONXFpuX0bx9xY/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equality of access to the digital world &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1WLcDjgme4m2yDMn-edBqlwGZx8eFIshr86M2UAtRyNk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The place of ethics in science &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FL1hp3NbP3HhqHZAKZSblsOJbrW1EzSsKN8c7KviW7A/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Learn how to Debate]]></title><description><![CDATA[How to successfully prepare for ILYMUN Each school has its own MUN (Model United Nations) club, whose members meet weekly to debate issues…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/debate-help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/debate-help/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;How to successfully prepare for ILYMUN&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each school has its own MUN (Model United Nations) club, whose members meet weekly to debate issues discussed in the UN, increasing their knowledge of the interconnected world we live in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We encourage all students participating in ILYMUN to thoroughly prepare themselves. It is the only way to reap benefits from the experience. Head over to the “Committees” page to discover the research reports the chairs have prepared for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Communication with the delegates you will be debating with at ILYMUN is also a key part of a good delegate’s preparation. This is why we will shortly make a list available to all delegates with delegates’ emails, names, country and committee assignments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are unfamiliar with the rules and procedures of UN debates, you will find two explanatory documents as well as a video below (click on them to view in full scale). If you want even more information, you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20181101190208/https://docs.google.com/document/d/1cTPkGrC2Ld0C8_q3aOjzo_qzDRNoPmpQs73ms8HLVjo/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; and read the document.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To ensure a high quality of debates, an External MUN Development team is dedicated to offering full assistance in building and/or developing MUN clubs for participating schools in need. If you are concerned, you may contact them through the ilymun support email address: support@ilymun.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2V1CpVOnuAY&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;720px&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;allowfullscreen&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/Rules-and-Procedures.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;../assets/ILYMUN-rules-and-procedure.pdf&quot;&gt;Click here to view the pdf version of the ILYMUN rules and procedures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Must know Concepts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;**Points &amp;#x26; Motions: **What are they and how are they used?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a guide for first time delegates who aren’t completely familiar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;with all the different&lt;/span&gt; _**&lt;/em&gt;points&lt;em&gt;**&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;or&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;**&lt;/em&gt;motions&lt;em&gt;**&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;at an MUN conference.&lt;/span&gt;_&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The difference between a motion and a point is who it concerns. A motion involves the entire committee, while a point only involves a chair or delegate. For this reason a motion requires a vote.  When a delegate proposes a motion, the chairs ask if there are any objections to the motion. If there are none, the motion is voted on. Neither points nor motions can interrupt speakers, unless it is a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;point of personal privilege&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;to do with the audibility of the speaker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;When a delegate proposes a motion, another delegate must second it before the chairs will consider it and ask if there are any objections to the motion.  If there are objections, then the motion is dropped. If there aren’t any objections, there is a vote, without abstentions.  The motion passes if there are more votes in favour of the motion than against. All motions can be overruled by the chair.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to extend debate time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If passed this motion extends the amount of time allocated to the current clause or amendment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to table the amendment or clause&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If this motion is passed debate on the current clause or amendment is stopped without a vote or postponed until later.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to reconsider an amendment or clause&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If this motion is passed debate on an amendment or clause that failed or has been tabled is resumed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to move to previous question&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If this motion passes debate on the current amendment or clause is stopped, there is a  vote and the debate moves on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Points:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a question for the delegate who has the floor. The chair will ask the delegate if she is open to any points of information. If she is, she can state how many questions she’ll entertain or even say “any and all”. The chairs then ask if there are any points of information in the house.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of personal privilege.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This point is only used if a delegate is experiencing discomfort or cannot hear the delegate talking. This is the only point or motion that can interrupt the speaker, if it refers to the audibility of the speaker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of parliamentary inquiry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A point of parliamentary inquiry is a question about the rules and procedures of a debate, and can only be asked when there is nobody on the floor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of order&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A point of order refers to when a chair or a delegate makes a mistake. For a chair, this could be that he has made an error in the procedures, and for a delegate, it might be that he is doing something that his country would not do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dressing]]></title><description><![CDATA[During ILYMUN, delegates and members of the organizing team are expected to have a professional attitude. This should reflect in their…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/dress/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/dress/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;During ILYMUN, delegates and members of the organizing team are expected to have a professional attitude. This should reflect in their clothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendees are requested to wear appropriate attire. Here is some inspiration on what to wear:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clothes are never a frivolity: they always mean something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~James Laver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/ilymun-website/static/media/dresscode.ab5d389e.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[International Court of Justice]]></title><description><![CDATA[What is the ICJ ? The International Court of Justice was created to act as a supreme judicial authority within the United Nations. It…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/international-court-of-justice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/international-court-of-justice/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the ICJ ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The International Court of Justice&lt;/strong&gt; was created to act as a supreme&lt;br&gt;
judicial authority within the United Nations. It ensures global justice and safeguards nations’ sovereignty by settling&lt;br&gt;
legal altercations presented to it by the Member States. It does so by considering previous treaties, international&lt;br&gt;
conventions and international law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ICJ at ILYMUN will help you view conflicts from a new perspective and will offer&lt;br&gt;
insight on international law and the proceedings of judicial cases. The ICJ is perfect for those interested in&lt;br&gt;
international relations, law or simply for those who want to try something new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;What is This Year’s Case ?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year’s case centres on the ethnic persecution of the Rohingya people in the Rakhine&lt;br&gt;
state by the Myanmar Republic. This has resulted in the mass migration of almost 700,000 individuals into the area of&lt;br&gt;
Cox’s Bazar, in Bangladesh. Consequently, this persecution has caused major problems for Bangladesh, as they have to&lt;br&gt;
provide refuge for the Rohingya people.&lt;br&gt;
The two teams of advocates will represent the following groups :&lt;br&gt;
– Applicant party: Bangladesh&lt;br&gt;
– Respondent party: Myanmar Republic&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Does the ICJ at ILYMUN Work ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ICJ is composed of&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 presidents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teams of advocates; each team consisting of two advocates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12-15 independent judges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both sides hold opening speeches to present both factual and legal evidence to the judges.&lt;br&gt;
The judges are given time to question the advocates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, each advocate team presents two to three witnesses. (Witnesses are approved by the&lt;br&gt;
Presidents of the ICJ prior to the conference.) Advocates are given the opportunity to interview witnesses and then judges&lt;br&gt;
can also question the witnesses or pose questions to the advocates regarding witnesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then advocates present closing statements. After this, the judges deliberate upon the information&lt;br&gt;
presented to them and compose a verdict expressing their judgment in the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do Advocates and Judges Prepare for the ICJ ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advocates&lt;/strong&gt; need to research the case and create a report (called a memorandum).&lt;br&gt;
They also suggest a list of 3-4 witnesses they would like to have at the trial. Finally, they create an evidence packet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Presidents of the ICJ&lt;/strong&gt; will work in partnership with the advocates to create&lt;br&gt;
and polish these documents and then post them on the ILYMUN website for judges to access. To access those documents, &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20181026101439/http://ilymun.org/committees/&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Judges&lt;/strong&gt; should read the documents posted by the Presidents of the ICJ to&lt;br&gt;
become familiar with the case, the witnesses and the evidence. It is expected that judges will act without bias, be reflective and innovative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presidents of the ICJ&lt;/strong&gt; will also guide the judges in their deliberation to help them evaluate&lt;br&gt;
legal documents and assure the quality of the final verdict.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do I Sign Up for the ICJ ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delegates who want to apply to the ICJ should be confident in their level of English. Advocates in&lt;br&gt;
particular should be confident public speakers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the challenging nature and limited places for this committee we ask delegates to apply for a&lt;br&gt;
role in the ICJ, by &lt;strong&gt;submitting a letter of motivation&lt;/strong&gt; which explains their previous MUN experiences and what makes them qualified&lt;br&gt;
for the role. Delegates should also state which role they prefer (judge or advocate) and if they are open to taking the alternative&lt;br&gt;
if they aren’t accepted for their first choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Applications must be accompanied by a &lt;strong&gt;letter of recommendation&lt;/strong&gt; from the delegates’ MUN Director. Send letters of&lt;br&gt;
application and recommendations by &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;FRIDAY, OCTOBER 12&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;any questions&lt;/strong&gt; about the ICJ to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20181026101439/mailto:kmalouda@islyon.org&quot;&gt;kmalouda@islyon.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[about]]></title><description><![CDATA[In 2015 the UN adopted the 17 Sustainable Development Goals, and set targets for 2030. Our conference addresses Goal 10. In defining this…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/about/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;In 2015 the UN adopted the 17 Sustainable Development Goals, and set targets for 2030. Our conference addresses Goal 10. In defining this goal, the UN explains that “Inequalities based on income, sex, age, disability, sexual orientation, race, class, ethnicity, religion and opportunity continue to persist across the world.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Economic growth is not enough to reduce these disparities. The gaps between the rich and the poor are growing bigger. It is clear that inequality is a serious threat to social and political stability as well as to the environment and sustained growth. Thus, inequalities within and among countries is one of our biggest challenges. According to the UN, “Inequality is not a matter of fate or chance and can be reversed through policies and reforms.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is our hope that in debating issues regarding empowerment, opportunity and the social and economic inclusion of all, the delegates of ILYMUN 2019 will draft these much-needed policies and reforms.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Contact]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/contact/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/contact/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[By Students for Students]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/parallax/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/parallax/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Press]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/press/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/press/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Our Team]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/team/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/team/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why ILYMUN?]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/values/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/values/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Beginnings]]></title><description><![CDATA[Far far away, behind the word mountains, far from the countries Vokalia and
Consonantia, there live the blind texts. Separated they live in…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/new-beginnings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/new-beginnings/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Far far away, behind the word mountains, far from the countries Vokalia and
Consonantia, there live the blind texts. Separated they live in Bookmarksgrove
right at the coast of the Semantics, a large language ocean. A small river named
Duden flows by their place and supplies it with the necessary regelialia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;On deer horse aboard tritely yikes and much&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Big Oxmox advised her not to do so, because there were thousands of bad
Commas, wild Question Marks and devious Semikoli, but the Little Blind Text
didn’t listen. She packed her seven versalia, put her initial into the belt and
made herself on the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This however showed weasel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well uncritical so misled&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;this is very interesting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Goodness much until that fluid owl&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she reached the first hills of the &lt;strong&gt;Italic Mountains&lt;/strong&gt;, she had a last
view back on the skyline of her hometown &lt;em&gt;Bookmarksgrove&lt;/em&gt;, the headline of
&lt;a href=&quot;http://google.com&quot;&gt;Alphabet Village&lt;/a&gt; and the subline of her own road, the Line
Lane. Pityful a rhetoric question ran over her cheek, then she continued her
way. On her way she met a copy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Overlaid the jeepers uselessly much excluding&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But nothing the copy said could convince her and so it didn’t take long until a
few insidious Copy Writers ambushed her, made her drunk with
&lt;a href=&quot;http://google.com&quot;&gt;Longe and Parole&lt;/a&gt; and dragged her into their agency, where
they abused her for their projects again and again. And if she hasn’t been
rewritten, then they are still using her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Far far away, behind the word mountains, far from the countries Vokalia and
Consonantia, there live the blind texts. Separated they live in Bookmarksgrove
right at the coast of the Semantics, a large language ocean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a paradisematic country, in which roasted parts of sentences fly into your
mouth. Even the all-powerful Pointing has no control about the blind texts it is
an almost unorthographic life One day however a small line of blind text by the
name of Lorem Ipsum decided to leave for the far World of Grammar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;According a funnily until pre-set or arrogant well cheerful&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Big Oxmox advised her not to do so, because there were thousands of bad
Commas, wild Question Marks and devious Semikoli, but the Little Blind Text
didn’t listen. She packed her seven versalia, put her initial into the belt and
made herself on the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So baboon this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mounted militant weasel gregariously admonishingly straightly hey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dear foresaw hungry and much some overhung&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rash opossum less because less some amid besides yikes jeepers frenetic
impassive fruitlessly shut&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she reached the first hills of the Italic Mountains, she had a last view
back on the skyline of her hometown Bookmarksgrove, the headline of Alphabet
Village and the subline of her own road, the Line Lane. Pityful a rhetoric
question ran over her cheek, then she continued her way. On her way she met a
copy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The copy warned the Little Blind Text, that where it came from it would have
been rewritten a thousand times and everything that was left from its origin
would be the word “and” and the Little Blind Text should turn around and
return to its own, safe country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But nothing the copy said could convince her and so it didn’t take long until a
few insidious Copy Writers ambushed her, made her drunk with Longe and Parole
and dragged her into their agency, where they abused her for their projects
again and again. And if she hasn’t been rewritten, then they are still using
her. Far far away, behind the word mountains, far from the countries Vokalia and
Consonantia, there live the blind texts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Silent delightfully including because before one up barring chameleon&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Separated they live in Bookmarksgrove right at the coast of the Semantics, a
large language ocean. A small river named Duden flows by their place and
supplies it with the necessary regelialia. It is a paradisematic country, in
which roasted parts of sentences fly into your mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even the all-powerful Pointing has no control about the blind texts it is an
almost unorthographic life One day however a small line of blind text by the
name of Lorem Ipsum decided to leave for the far World of Grammar. The Big Oxmox
advised her not to do so, because there were thousands of bad Commas, wild
Question Marks and devious Semikoli, but the Little Blind Text didn’t listen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Wherever far wow thus a squirrel raccoon jeez jaguar this from along&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She packed her seven versalia, put her initial into the belt and made herself on
the way. When she reached the first hills of the Italic Mountains, she had a
last view back on the skyline of her hometown Bookmarksgrove, the headline of
Alphabet Village and the subline of her own road, the Line Lane. Pityful a
rhetoric question ran over her cheek, then she continued her way. On her way she
met a copy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Slapped cozy a that lightheartedly and far&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The copy warned the Little Blind Text, that where it came from it would have
been rewritten a thousand times and everything that was left from its origin
would be the word “and” and the Little Blind Text should turn around and return
to its own, safe country. But nothing the copy said could convince her and so it
didn’t take long until a few insidious Copy Writers ambushed her, made her drunk
with Longe and Parole and dragged her into their agency, where they abused her
for their projects again and again.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My Second Post!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wow! I love blogging so much already. Did you know that “despite its name, salted duck eggs can also be made from
chicken eggs, though the…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/my-second-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/my-second-post/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 23:46:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Wow! I love blogging so much already.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you know that “despite its name, salted duck eggs can also be made from
chicken eggs, though the taste and texture will be somewhat different, and the
egg yolk will be less rich.”?
(&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Salted_duck_egg&quot;&gt;Wikipedia Link&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I didn’t either.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is my first post on my new fake blog! How exciting! I’m sure I’ll write a lot more interesting things in the future. Oh, and here’s a…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/hello-world/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post on my new fake blog! How exciting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m sure I’ll write a lot more interesting things in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and here’s a great quote from this Wikipedia on
&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Salted_duck_egg&quot;&gt;salted duck eggs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A salted duck egg is a Chinese preserved food product made by soaking duck
eggs in brine, or packing each egg in damp, salted charcoal. In Asian
supermarkets, these eggs are sometimes sold covered in a thick layer of salted
charcoal paste. The eggs may also be sold with the salted paste removed,
wrapped in plastic, and vacuum packed. From the salt curing process, the
salted duck eggs have a briny aroma, a gelatin-like egg white and a
firm-textured, round yolk that is bright orange-red in color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span
      class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot;
      style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;  max-width: 590px;&quot;
    &gt;
      &lt;a
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-link&quot;
    href=&quot;/static/8058f3f26913fea3b6a89a73344fe94a/2b40c/salty_egg.jpg&quot;
    style=&quot;display: block&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;
    rel=&quot;noopener&quot;
  &gt;
    &lt;span
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot;
    style=&quot;padding-bottom: 75%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&apos;data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wBDABALDA4MChAODQ4SERATGCgaGBYWGDEjJR0oOjM9PDkzODdASFxOQERXRTc4UG1RV19iZ2hnPk1xeXBkeFxlZ2P/2wBDARESEhgVGC8aGi9jQjhCY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2P/wgARCAAPABQDASIAAhEBAxEB/8QAFgABAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAMB/8QAFwEAAwEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEEBf/aAAwDAQACEAMQAAABgik0dXC//8QAGRABAAMBAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAQACEhEy/9oACAEBAAEFAkqW2DlnRj73yf/EABcRAQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAREkH/2gAIAQMBAT8B1WX/xAAWEQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEQL/2gAIAQIBAT8Bi6f/xAAbEAABBAMAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAQIRISIxMv/aAAgBAQAGPwK9GNocyS8hCj//xAAbEAADAQADAQAAAAAAAAAAAAABESEAMUGBof/aAAgBAQABPyGxNMfrLHmCDZmAzzvJJDjEQCHv/9oADAMBAAIAAwAAABDIL//EABYRAQEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAERAP/aAAgBAwEBPxARhylZv//EABgRAAIDAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABESFR/9oACAECAQE/EFoktI//xAAdEAEBAAICAwEAAAAAAAAAAAABEQAxIWFBcYHh/9oACAEBAAE/EEbMLQ0fMHDVaPIXyI4pk4JUnWacNCtO8ojDE9TGIYES7/Jn/9k=&apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;
  &gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;img
        class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot;
        alt=&quot;Chinese Salty Egg&quot;
        title=&quot;Chinese Salty Egg&quot;
        src=&quot;/static/8058f3f26913fea3b6a89a73344fe94a/c739e/salty_egg.jpg&quot;
        srcset=&quot;/static/8058f3f26913fea3b6a89a73344fe94a/8ee9c/salty_egg.jpg 148w,
/static/8058f3f26913fea3b6a89a73344fe94a/ebbe7/salty_egg.jpg 295w,
/static/8058f3f26913fea3b6a89a73344fe94a/c739e/salty_egg.jpg 590w,
/static/8058f3f26913fea3b6a89a73344fe94a/5413e/salty_egg.jpg 885w,
/static/8058f3f26913fea3b6a89a73344fe94a/4efde/salty_egg.jpg 1180w,
/static/8058f3f26913fea3b6a89a73344fe94a/2b40c/salty_egg.jpg 2048w&quot;
        sizes=&quot;(max-width: 590px) 100vw, 590px&quot;
        loading=&quot;lazy&quot;
      /&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>