<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Gatsby Starter Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[A starter blog demonstrating what Gatsby can do.]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 22:53:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[ILYMUN 2020]]></title><description><![CDATA[2020 will be the eighth consecutive year in which the International School of Lyon and the Cité Scolaire Internationale de Lyon collaborate…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/about/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;2020 will be the eighth consecutive year in which the International School of Lyon and the Cité Scolaire Internationale de Lyon collaborate to organise ILYMUN. The conference will take place the 30th, 31st January and 1st of February, in the prestigious ‘Hôtel de Région Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes’ (1 Esplanade François Mitterrand, 69269 Lyon, Cedex 02). We have invited keen and bright high school pupils to join us to debate and take action!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2015 the UN adopted 17 goals, the Sustainable Development Goals, and set targets for 2030 in order to improve the quality of life on the planet. The theme of our conference this year, ‘Water: A Thirst for Change’, will focus on Goal 6, Clean water and sanitation, and Goal 14, Life below water. The importance of these two goals is unparalleled. As the UN states, “Water is at the core of sustainable development and is critical for socio-economic development, energy and food production, healthy ecosystems and for human survival itself.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that by involving youth in finding solutions and taking action, we can make a difference. Therefore, in addition to our core MUN committees, we will once again host the Action Assembly, in which students represent themselves rather than countries in order to work towards real change in their local communities, striving for change through direct action. Additionally, ILYMUN will also be hosting the ‘Youth Conference’ for middle school students from the Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will also offer the Model International Court of Justice (ICJ), a forum that mediates conflicts between two nations by reflecting on treaties, international conventions, and international law. The ICJ is a unique and enriching experience for delegates who wish to try something different to ordinary committees, particularly for those interested in pursuing a career in law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, we vow to make ILYMUN 2020 an unforgettable and thrilling experience for all its participants!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;History&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking inspiration from FERMUN in Geneva and THIMUN in the Hague, two students from the Cité Scolaire Internationale, Pierre Mohamed and Kaelan Tardy, reached out to students at the International School of Lyon in order to organise the first ILYMUN conference in 2013. Most of the schools participating in that first conference are now regular participants in our annual conferences and many have gone on to form their own MUN clubs and conferences inspired by ILYMUN. We’re delighted to see these developments: signalling that communities are truly working together towards the bettering of our world!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Our Values&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;1. Inciting Action&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our core objective is to bring about change. Outside of the MUN debates, we hope to extend the resolutions our students conceive, and apply them to the real world. Indeed, by taking action, we hope to contribute to bettering our international community by giving life to delegates’ ideas, with hope of striving towards a greater future. In the light of such, we encourage our delegates to educate themselves regarding these issues, both local and global, and to directly act upon them, externalising ILYMUN’s outreach upon our impaired societies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;2. Enriching Education&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that MUN conferences should aim to educate the participants, providing them with essential skills such as public speaking, collaboration with others and critical thinking. MUN opens one’s mind and encourages in-depth reflections on our complex world. ILYMUN helps students grow and become global citizens. Here is a quote from one of our friends at INOMUN in Lille that captures our view of MUN: “The aim of debating is to resolve problems with words, without violence, without deaths. We, high school students, are the next generation. We have to act, we have to do something. An MUN conference won’t literally change things, but it is a way to sharpen our critical minds and our intelligence in order to take over our parents’ generation. In order to bring peace.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;3. Constant Innovation&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ILYMUN has matured since its inception by the virtue of original projects, developed every year. Of course, the central issue of the conference varies from year to year, with new branches and new committees created to bring diversification and an improved experience. Undeniably, the feedback from you, fellow participants, permits us to improve an important number of aspects of the conference, making it finer each year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;4. Human Experience&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most diplomats tell you that the most efficient decisions, those which actually change the world, are taken in convivial moments after a day of debate. This is wholly legitimate. Therefore, we keep in mind that an MUN conference is an opportune moment to meet new friends. A few essential factors, unique to ILYMUN, allow you to have real exchanges: small committees (from 20 to 100 persons), country delegations made up of different schools, housing with host families and, of course, social events!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;5. By Students, For Students&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though a very small team of adults supervises our agenda and the organisation of ILYMUN, every aspect of our conference — the vision, planning and execution — is done by high school students who are doing their best to provide middle school and high school delegates and their MUN directors the best possible MUN experience and a professional conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;6. Social and Ecological Engagements&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bearing in mind the ILYMUN 2016 conference resolutions to tackle Climate Change, we take concrete action to save the Planet, by respecting environmental values. We use a minimal amount of paper and transfer to digital as frequently as possible. We strive to be role models for a green conference.&lt;br/&gt;
The past several years we also have committed to debating the work and the value of various NGOs in our General Assemblies. Delegates then make a vote that leads to real action. The NGO that wins the majority vote receives a financial donation from ILYMUN. This donation is made possible by the wonderful support of our sponsors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;7. Sponsorship&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To make ILYMUN truly outstanding, we rely on generous sponsorship from institutions as well as private companies and individuals. We are currently sponsored by the Région Auvergne Rhône-Alpes who have generously provided their premises for the event. By financially helping ILYMUN, you will be effectively helping us reach our goals of providing a professional conference and encouraging young people to work towards positive changes in our world. For more information, click here to view our sponsor’s brochure (in PDF format). If you or your company are interested, our Public Relations Team is here to answer all of the questions you might have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Contact: tom.badou@csianglo.org&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Action Assembly]]></title><description><![CDATA[A unique committee where your voice is heard! What is Action Assembly ? Action Assembly is very different from the rest of the committees at…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/action-assembly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/action-assembly/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A unique committee where your voice is heard!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What is Action Assembly ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Action Assembly is very different from the rest of the committees at ILYMUN as you will be expressing yourself more personally. You will be debating issues with a more down-to-earth and relatable approach as the motions and objectives are chosen in order to allow individual reflection and change. Most committees debate in the name of nations and debate real-time UN subjects and motions, on the other hand, we will be debating motions that directly impact our way of life and delegates will be representing themselves (or cities, associations, corporations of their choice depending on the theme).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What is this year’s theme ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; This year’s theme is water. We will be focusing on three main topics: water overconsumption (including meat consumption, household water use, etc…) water pollution (including fast fashion, agriculture, plastic use…) and finally access to sanitation. We really hope the delegates will feel passionate about the exchanges that will take place between themselves and will be eager to keep the conversation going after the conference in order to take true action!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What are we going to do ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; In order to see the real changes we can make, and to take real action, the delegates will be preparing a 10 point chart at the end of our three days of debate, listing the main actions we can individually take to help with these water issues. We also think a recap video of Action Assembly’s debate as well as a few posters, could be extremely powerful in order to raise awareness on the subject. The goal would be to post these on the ILYMUN platforms and distribute them (charts and posters) in your schools and communities. We truly want everyone to feel concerned, and reflect on their ways of life, which is what we need to change!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;How do we prepare for the Action Assembly ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  We have prepared a Research Report to give the delegates an overall idea of what the debate will be like, and to enlighten them on the research they should be doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  We expect our delegates to have thought about their personal opinions on the topics, as well as have done research on one or more corporations, associations, cities they will be representing (during days 2 &amp;#x26; 3)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Why should YOU join the Action Assembly ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; This is the committee where your own voice is heard. This is the committee that actually works towards real change. Being confronted with various opinions leads to truly enriching and relevant conversations rather than debating as assigned countries which, although being challenging and inspiring, is a form of debate that restricts the delegates to a specific point of view and makes it harder to relate on a personal level to the debated motions. The topic of ILYMUN 2020 being “water”, an extremely relevant and important subject of today’s world, we find it particularly interesting to debate in our own names as so much change can be made on an individual level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whoever you are, you should be part of Action Assembly, and promote action in the world!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Committees & Issues Debated]]></title><description><![CDATA[ILYMUN 2020 General Assembly The Respect of the Fundamental Rights endowed to all by the charter of the United Nations Security Council…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/committees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/committees/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2020&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1qkUgtF8VtI-1rtgB1ZAuAVdSUOHjYUrFGgHNi0uC324/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The Respect of the Fundamental Rights endowed to all by the charter of the United Nations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1JsveYWP5H9_hPvWZlhjYUosXyXTh7l1sLH6W-7rEM-0/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Tackling Organised Crime at Sea &quot;&gt;Tackling Organised Crime at Sea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/17SVWDQ_uaFZxhdxW6MiUrr4cEnfqxxPsbCxDglPPlzY/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;The South China Sea &quot;&gt;The South China Sea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1XMPc_AiXF1QibUSPGouG9jNkn2XEclrl_YDzNgApQn4/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Water Scarcity &quot;&gt;Water Scarcity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Historical Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1YVIrD42zWaigMAFF2QxRav8nQ9dZj3hZ10GpQeoIpLw/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Suez Canal Crisis: 1956 &quot;&gt;Suez Canal Crisis: 1956&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1rtsQs_y3W0uccXbD_Mlx7GPTuGen2f2bJNcpeRll6-k/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Turkish Invasion of Cyprus: 1974&quot;&gt;Turkish Invasion of Cyprus: 1974&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1_aOEZuLHU-KEI6lQgVXH09LYT8hOycn4pRk1Pqy8LA0/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Falkland Islands War: 1982&quot;&gt;Falkland Islands War: 1982  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Territorial&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/16Yv5rSotOESM3ESoxtYSor9CtWPM5iN6qiouzBRPxQs/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Arctic Waters &quot;&gt;Arctic Waters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1S47htOtgxU56JlH6hLHm6dIDKYL59G2f8qop15aLne0/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Transboundary Waters &quot;&gt;Transboundary Waters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Environmental&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1D8BkTOW14pbXrERnWClSa1MOSvHyR3ixQPJucZDVJCI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;The Great Pacific Garbage Patch&quot;&gt;The Great Pacific Garbage Patch&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1PL-COO5IIY6th27sHuunqKCqFjEUNW-SkMF2lSaj1o4/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Conservation and Management of Freshwater Sources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Science and Technology&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1G2OO5h3k56ENMaXY158aoE8XTJCXFKqHgzvq-4Aumcs/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Improving Ocean Health&quot;&gt;Improving Ocean Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1steW5wK0iB_DctxmWKjZnpTIUhyqrFOm4zVEn90g4D0/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Water as a Sustainable Resource&quot;&gt;Water as a Sustainable Resource&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Human Rights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1OpCTl6sUNMTpVZ8F7NlfdauIqSP7F1TjEvxn5BExgcA/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Embedding Gender Equity in Water Policies&quot;&gt;Embedding Gender Equity in Water Policies&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1_xLsKUgbaDSIV1CI18O4ouTBWeWwtCm3PCBI4J-0tBE/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Governance of Indigenous Peoples Water Supply&quot;&gt;Governance of Indigenous Peoples Water Supply&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;UNDP&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/15WuF9QVp0clLdh1BAxxosNd4PX0PEP9F3WQSgNfBYTs/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Disaster Relief &quot;&gt;Disaster Relief&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1mZgAcfJ2adKVegNCUZl5SSiJlFjw6UNINqFQ5HtJ9Z8/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Extraction, Trade and Allocation of Water Sources &quot;&gt;Extraction, Trade and Allocation of Water Sources &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1M1Mv6_4UK-YbsPTfpvQyhfL71HMySBDHhBFpPDBgp4c/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Prevention and Management of Droughts &quot;&gt;Prevention and Management of Droughts&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;World Health Organisation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1teuKYMitqt_9ZuiD2nPVx-4WW1e8kTdGH-FGAw4GX90/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Guaranteeing Water Safety &quot;&gt;Guaranteeing Water Safety&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1nW9UvvyNYT9Q1SOMJCjE1kaQSvBwpTvEeEdHZ9U7mD0/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Water Scarcity &quot;&gt;Water Scarcity&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Action Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1SXlsah_LyaPdqHB_bBY3ARONZI2tucI3YQebTmstCGg/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Water Over-Consumption; Water Pollution; Sanitation&quot;&gt;Water Over-Consumption; Water Pollution; Sanitation&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Conference: Focus on Islands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1LjxKqRXCoe-9Whd7gE-UZO6XGdFE2DlLPp4S27_vIEI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Special Conference: Focus on Islands &quot;&gt;Special Conference: Complete Research Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2019&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1qkUgtF8VtI-1rtgB1ZAuAVdSUOHjYUrFGgHNi0uC324/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The Respect of the Fundamental Rights endowed to all by the charter of the United Nations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1JXxAY4CA24UUkkP_GXeS0xmZeEOyUQis8b0RZzABVFI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The issue of the Rohingya people&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Bk0rYlO2twnUMtdF4O-LP50TsrBkdgufrcv7KnGXTNI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Working towards a unified Bosnia Herzegovina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/18hupxkrwzHScvhqzwxk6pJdrg2ELnQgUEOkJOt5GL60/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The right of nations to have nuclear arms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Historical Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/15jSnRJdVmLW6Q8G2gXQFsNLZLSbSuR24yyJyMUlvWyA/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The recognition of the state of Israel and its membership in the UN; May 1948&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/103B3qeFI_Cpgl5duP-LEMJUmqqx-asGS-ME7fEEZVfw/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Drafting the Nuclear Non Proliferation Treaty; August 25, 1967&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1QWu3Mve1AM5KwXo44uzsrLrHTZXMFOL647kCM5ReBVg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Rwandan genocide; April 30, 1994&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Territorial&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1vx2_SiD5jDIl4q8egVI6O8CQevIKeovu?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Sharing global resources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This committee will work towards the creation of multiple resolutions regarding specific resources (water, minerals, forests, oil, etc.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Environmental&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1U8cf6xz2wrHoDLiY8RCxvKtesgxBw9eI53Ca6z-z_78/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The pollution “market”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FqmpqxPqeKCTYneaEkjQO2JwNzcrBfn3UKF3yaVv1uI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Sustainable development: a balance between economic growth and the protection of natural resources and ecosystems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Economic&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1LemTIRZi04H3lZ_wmLfVXPOHycZmEOtQj_7mRtiz_N4/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Equality in the workplace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1V_1XyON8PeQRiLjGuj6oF7g5cxVBwQnL6e0n2Cvu_NI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Reducing poverty as a step towards equity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Social&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1gB_iBYlp2Y94Hb7GCLz-xiD0EapQeOuoBcQJowRXry4/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Reducing discrimination&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1NppMAPJd3eL2EJZyIi_hrcJGylNP4mGPMQYF4ygaaL0/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Universal healthcare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Human Rights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/15cjGASjC7M3KYvXZpdfN7TuideWbrrqNoFstYLZ1e8g/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Police brutality and discrimination of minorities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1aeWUQiIxcmpIqkjvQdKMje5wDA689QazK14q_IgEbpE/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The protection and the rights of migrants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Conference: Focus on Children&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1WxAz5GyxWxopmVKHk4CrSZDzGBMgnxGYxg-wehL_H9o/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Healthcare and mortality rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1F_TauSK7R69Atw3TLb9eVE7h92Uw2wafzVdDrK5ZDqU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Protecting the rights of the child&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1tZDIYwpEVeVViKR7CUm9tT2pMXNng1h0p3GK8jj1YvM/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Action Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1vv7VzZJn6NxrkroLLDJklqCBCoMpU9lI/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Gender inequalities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1gKMtw16cSMB8GVLk4zcqFfpEr0VeDzwT/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Unequal access to culture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/14HGBEwQ27aglY0XsY0taXj-CVV_4mZc8/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Unequal access to health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Conference: Focus on Women&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/12yJnfdllyckCDxFvDEvetgzuKSxD6KZcpe5Tzgo5NuQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Reducing gender inequalities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1xmQUWaLW3abFrF_4Oe7sA0oCTSbe8elKDFYeTKuYBuc/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Empowering women&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2018&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;ilymun2018&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;card card-body&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1mZMZYBlwidT05QvGHQ9xlfu0ekoi9rk6zjsPJEv4Uyg&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Securing cities against acts of terrorism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WfCUn79gEK1wfHmG1iDHeQaTSsYIH2L8S5ot35Eyvtw&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection of civilians in civilian war zones, Aleppo, Syria&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1G21BI9YQUw3X0Wzb3CU1ZHbwXZthTG8pHpem6GYvEf4&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question of Chechnya, Russia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1Hvv0HmaHtO5PgfuZctBPu9WvQX3wCZ3GvYiumvQ70fQ&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Securing cities against acts of terrorism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WfCUn79gEK1wfHmG1iDHeQaTSsYIH2L8S5ot35Eyvtw&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Historical Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Korean War: June 25th 1950&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1ofAMq6jOINqo5MDwylQlruItBGY1i1JaagcZC7vIzy8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cambodia: 30th April 1977&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=15gfOuBJU6axa2A5978mhCZvjUJ9gW9P7cDwLs58J9Ws&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cultural&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approaches to preserving cultural heritage within urban areas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1yQVM_FBsfvqMmsU4ztByieBj1uoU2qSZ0S8jADA8-1k/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protecting UNESCO historical cities from ravages of war and siege&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1iOE6PqVWBeYm6bvlaMxOqTPltoLvGguDPOrr4Ur5vJ0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Development&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The issue of informal settlement in rapidly developing urban areas in LEDCs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=15vGmQnWv0Vhcv8KOztD0ux42-YId_QUiADNYeYn-5M0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The implementation of the goals of Agenda21 in urban areas of LEDCs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1ONzB7-WWQ1mkQf7vn63qCMDF_hxJ48XSqPRoSXeRXl4&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;ECOSOC&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting the demands of an ageing population in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1chez1NA9OfuKeifwQvAplvj1tMU8qBnE23NZvlBfdCc&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Problems faced by megacities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=14zZ5vGypUp7YCgsPJy4EJO2tYHmDOrbUM4zXtzHWsk8&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Environmental&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Measures supporting cleaner and greener cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=12ZaZ0-wPsHgWUwj5i-PGyW5r8z-eqR2sAuhRyFcDGfE&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Climate change and disaster risk in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1ftJKk7jDNfgueYvPC96v_tIQq4wZegQ4U9htpbzG8n0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Science and Technology&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The use of renewable energy sources in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WcB2lZiM8ni9MdoGWdgwhny7rNA3NgJEiqYeu8t33L8&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question of smart cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WbKnKi6XCHrhC7rC0Xjy-d9VuHVqdr_Ca1US3FKAjy0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Human Rights Conference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protecting the rights of refugees in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1_CcCkOBmwn4yufRlR7562WnY-r_K5IQCp0UnBSMD4Dg&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Providing equal access to basic services&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1IW8y1Juw0iq0f1TJWIBqsUtejFS4F1PL5COOCFjgVPg&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;International Court of Justice&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;War crimes in Aleppo, Syria&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1sl5eCsLmO3_NCGIemvTk-T2U-H5hXLd4&quot;&gt;Click here to access related documents&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Action Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Integration of marginalised people&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1NBnTTprGfyHc6d5KFvxza-CZ4r1NkitEOELSjdo5nnQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Integration of young migrants in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=12qfnMMEA1NnHMBmipwSDE90fj6SOMRc8GMBM_Q7fqQ0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cities studied:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1okaRCumLKkeNyRZ3nWfLZcVGWRiiEl2zfN9Z0IXB1Oo&quot;&gt;Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1QgSdg_L12vo-wz9M2rEJskW8mcZHR6cCblHMt2oMBJw&quot;&gt;Mumbai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1YoxL2mqNX6s9I4AmWEjr5snIj0O4Lv2DX_dqnJeDElQ&quot;&gt;Nairobi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=15GFPaeEvgWaLs-1zRL_Eh8oz9aXs31xCUgVYa5eM6pY&quot;&gt;Paris&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1wmM2UqYtYNEqzEjyeOsGGrm_EjcyvUc89CkYlTB2s8Q&quot;&gt;Tehran&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/a/csianglo.org/document/d/1FrMZtA-JTyhmuWY7r1KR9aQkanWa624tayZhtzNhDXU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2017&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;ilymun2017&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;card card-body&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1JpfiHrOpacGmjmENI21GCwWCWs_TIxGUhWpqf2FvjyE/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technological governance and democracy &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fFy1aYFiNdMknKTYWEMKZAm0wf1vN6b7U-9lSfw9pLo/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cyber warfare &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1L-ddWxrcGid-6M8u50kyifalEp0q1ZEMk7OQPSnGWGw/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Issue of security vs. privacy &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1SATkNofvVAD0ya_kvjteKJhl_UCql-Mr3Oj0z-xhzAA/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting heritage sites from armed conflicts &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1PYhItq2k8Ivk7c3NCOxN7Yfsuj9QrB0hKBnIt_-Mvf8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cultural Memory&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mass media’s effect on culture &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/194KxwpDGT188KWo9nR35hHJlZPpZDKOrXBpi05NKE9E/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting heritage sites for and from tourism &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CutMrkE8Ir6P8Mi9PDb_NkTMMR7c0_yBFykZNKZuzb0/edit?pli=1&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Claims to historical artifacts and documents &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1gSQQLI_spdai3CQcy5QREEGCg4xKb1qPzKi4pnvGrOY/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Resource Management&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The issue of the “brain drain” &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1SoEDeW2_gExktLlmlgySDUVmzkuLXHVi-0oNq8x1MN8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing food distribution &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Mzok1oXPNmea4IHnLun3Hk5dSGD99KvxTjHm137FWcg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing ocean resources &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fruxIZRd14gTQyColguNlt9aEH0xh8MXHc8_9hPoDTQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EcoSoc&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reducing technological disparities to promote economic equality &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FOu9K0sf-mR-DK_rQx7XmQ7co-W8YzBSTabXa0qlUSQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Economic power of technology &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1cPK5M5lQ8nJxrpiy2PYax2vRjjngl1CE4dB81SRQslM/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fighting poverty and inequality in a globalized society &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1wJTKM2eaxAqzEtsRXiDmbQcUSpSZUNYyyRPgvzROYLA/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cultural Identity&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting and promoting indigenous cultures &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Oy7pXLwl4EBTnj1Sl1sflq4IC4UxifncOZXVOOYa3qk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining cultural identity in a globalized world &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FDbZI44kTnZ0yblKXa6UhrZs6GXeb1-9lM6ZxtzTNKk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting human diversity in the face of biotechnology &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1pmF2MVwCxDRyFrpJHsnv4Ab-vXxhgMzeOBdzRRKRghg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Migration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fighting human trafficking and providing safe migration &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/11ebC2Xr67S4895I1hNRLwUOETtefDb9s9dnwroBFJ4w/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rights of refugees &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B0a_hZsHRAFFbWhqa1JxdUNjUF9maTNTdWFZWWFKUEVZVzRF/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The role of borders and freedom of movement &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1V6BbkQoi9qlu8Lhjff8N9kVgfo36j5NZnBrcVt8Oh0M/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Human Rights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promoting gender equality &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1g-_PCbeJv_IA15Pate7STp8G8oApiZAu-koj4aeWQvM/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liberty of thought and expression &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/14ZZb2OLROlVcw6a-91BSRn57speIPU0XXb5EStqZ2Lg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promoting self-determination &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/11NUHdUJe4QTtWpOfK4X1c64AvQr1K9bjX6Vt2m0wSBU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Science and Technology&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication, technology, and extremism &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/14XEiC-S6xIkpkyWDJmOT7IXcxgZm1AONXFpuX0bx9xY/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equality of access to the digital world &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1WLcDjgme4m2yDMn-edBqlwGZx8eFIshr86M2UAtRyNk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The place of ethics in science &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FL1hp3NbP3HhqHZAKZSblsOJbrW1EzSsKN8c7KviW7A/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Learn how to Debate]]></title><description><![CDATA[How to successfully prepare for ILYMUN To guarantee the excellence and the effective functioning of our ILYMUN debates, prior to the event…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/debate-help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/debate-help/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;How to successfully prepare for ILYMUN&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To guarantee the excellence and the effective functioning of our ILYMUN debates, prior to the event, we greatly encourage all students partaking in the conference to thoroughly prepare themselves. This will enable all to reap benefit from the experience!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To help our delegates in preparing for the conference, we have produced an effective five-step plan of action, to enable students to arrive at the conference in full confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Investigate your country’s background profile:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Better start somewhere! Try looking into the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Political situation and active positioning; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Its interaction with neighbouring countries, the former’s influence, conflicts…; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Statistical facts and data: life expectancy, literacy rates, CO2 emissions, access to water…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; remember to follow current and ongoing actuality around your country, grasping current political tensions, newly introduced measures…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. UN Committee basics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to research your committee and its particular relevance with ILYMUN’s general theme, ‘Water: a thirst for change’. Look into:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  How does it differentiate itself from other UN committees? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  What are the committee’s current activities, actions and engagements? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  What is your country’s involvement and interactions with the UN committee?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. RRR: Read the Research Reports:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your committee’s research reports have for objective of supplying a general background and impression of your allocated UN committee’s topic, actuality and basic data. This step is crucial for understanding the topic at hand. Look out for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  The core issues of your topic; Key terms; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Data concerning other countries in the committee; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Future steps and issues to tackle; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Further reading linked in the research reports by your chairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Grapple your country’s positioning:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the debate, you’ll be representing your country and promoting its engagements. Look into:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Active engagements and policies; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Past issues revolving around the topic; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Identify allied countries and research accords; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  If there is lacking information for your country, research neighbouring countries’ situation(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These steps will enable you to begin thinking of potential resolutions to exhibit during the debates. Bear in mind, you should aim to produce action! How can this follow through in your resolutions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Familiarise yourself with the rules of procedure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a key component towards guaranteeing a delegate’s effective preparation towards the ILYMUN conference. Bearing in mind, the delegates are free to question their respective chairs before and during the conference for all their doubts and concerns. Chairs are here to help!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Peer below to find an exhaustive explanation of procedures during an ILYMUN type-debate;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  The following video equally provides a helpful visualisation of the main rules of procedure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RQIbx4s8YTw&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;720px&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;allowfullscreen&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/Rules-and-Procedures.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;../assets/ILYMUN-rules-and-procedure.pdf&quot;&gt;Click here to view the pdf version of the ILYMUN rules and procedures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Must know Concepts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Points &amp;#x26; Motions: What are they and how are they used?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a guide for first time delegates who aren’t completely familiar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;with all the different&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;or&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;motions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;at an MUN conference.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The difference between a motion and a point is who it concerns. A motion involves the entire committee, while a point only involves a chair or delegate. For this reason a motion requires a vote.  When a delegate proposes a motion, the chairs ask if there are any objections to the motion. If there are none, the motion is voted on. Neither points nor motions can interrupt speakers, unless it is a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;point of personal privilege&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;to do with the audibility of the speaker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Motions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;When a delegate proposes a motion, another delegate must second it before the chairs will consider it and ask if there are any objections to the motion.  If there are objections, then the motion is dropped. If there aren’t any objections, there is a vote, without abstentions.  The motion passes if there are more votes in favour of the motion than against. All motions can be overruled by the chair.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to extend debate time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If passed this motion extends the amount of time allocated to the current clause or amendment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to table the amendment or clause&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If this motion is passed debate on the current clause or amendment is stopped without a vote or postponed until later.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to reconsider an amendment or clause&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If this motion is passed debate on an amendment or clause that failed or has been tabled is resumed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to move to previous question&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If this motion passes debate on the current amendment or clause is stopped, there is a  vote and the debate moves on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Points:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a question for the delegate who has the floor. The chair will ask the delegate if she is open to any points of information. If she is, she can state how many questions she’ll entertain or even say “any and all”. The chairs then ask if there are any points of information in the house.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of personal privilege.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This point is only used if a delegate is experiencing discomfort or cannot hear the delegate talking. This is the only point or motion that can interrupt the speaker, if it refers to the audibility of the speaker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of parliamentary inquiry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A point of parliamentary inquiry is a question about the rules and procedures of a debate, and can only be asked when there is nobody on the floor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of order&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A point of order refers to when a chair or a delegate makes a mistake. For a chair, this could be that he has made an error in the procedures, and for a delegate, it might be that he is doing something that his country would not do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;MUN Support:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, to ensure a high quality of debates, an External MUN Development team is dedicated to offering full assistance in building and/or developing MUN clubs for participating schools in need. If you are concerned, you may contact them through the ILYMUN support email address: support@ilymun.org&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dressing]]></title><description><![CDATA[During ILYMUN, delegates and members of the organising team are expected to have a professional attitude. This should reflect in their…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/dress/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/dress/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;During ILYMUN, delegates and members of the organising team are expected to have a professional attitude. This should reflect in their clothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendees are requested to wear appropriate attire. Here is some inspiration on what to wear:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Clothes mean nothing until someone lives in them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ &lt;em&gt;Marc Jacobs&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/ilymun-website/static/media/dresscode.ab5d389e.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[International Court of Justice]]></title><description><![CDATA[What is the ICJ ? The International Court of Justice was created to act as a supreme judicial authority within the United Nations. It…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/international-court-of-justice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/international-court-of-justice/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the ICJ ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The International Court of Justice&lt;/strong&gt; was created to act as a supreme&lt;br&gt;
judicial authority within the United Nations. It ensures global justice and safeguards nations’ sovereignty by settling legal altercations presented to it by the Member States. It does so by considering previous treaties, international conventions and international law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ICJ at ILYMUN will help you view conflicts from a new perspective and will offer insight on international law and the proceedings of judicial cases. The ICJ is perfect for those interested in international relations, law or simply for those who want to try something new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;What is This Year’s Case ?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year’s case is Egypt versus Ethiopia, in the conflict over the Grand Ethiopian Renaissance Dam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The two teams of advocates will represent the following groups :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Applicant party: Egypt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Respondent party: Ethiopia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Does the ICJ at ILYMUN Work ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The International Court of Justice is composed of:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- &lt;strong&gt;The Presidency:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two Presidents. This year they are represented by Helen Roka and Horia Barabas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- &lt;strong&gt;The Advocacy:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An Applicant and a Respondent party, both represented by 2 advocates each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- &lt;strong&gt;The Jurisdiction:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A court of 15-17 independent judges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both advocate parties hold opening speeches, to present both factual and legal evidence to the judges. The judges are given time to question the advocates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, each advocate team presents two to four witnesses. (Witnesses are approved by the Presidents of the ICJ prior to the conference.) Advocates are given the opportunity to interview witnesses and then judges can also question the witnesses or pose questions to the advocates regarding witnesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then advocates present closing statements. After this, the judges deliberate upon the information presented to them and compose a verdict expressing their judgment in the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do Advocates and Judges Prepare for the ICJ ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advocates&lt;/strong&gt; need to research the case and create a report (called a memorandum). They also suggest a list of 3-4 witnesses they would like to have at the trial. Finally, they create an evidence packet. The 2 parties collaborate together to create a stipulation. In sum, both teams prepare by&lt;strong&gt;*&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Gathering evidence&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Bringing in “witnesses”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Writing a stipulation, together&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Writing a memorandum&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_*__&lt;/strong&gt;unbiased help and guidance from Presidents as well as templates are provided._&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Presidents of the ICJ&lt;/strong&gt; will work in partnership with the advocates to create and polish these documents and then share them with the opposing advocates and the judges and/or post them on the ILYMUN website for all to access.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Judges&lt;/strong&gt; should read the documents shared and posted by the Presidents of the ICJ to become familiar with the case, the witnesses and the evidence. It is expected that judges will act without bias, be reflective and innovative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presidents of the ICJ&lt;/strong&gt; will also guide the judges in their &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;deliberation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to help them evaluate legal documents and assure the quality of the final verdict.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do I Sign Up for the ICJ ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delegates who want to apply to the ICJ should be confident in their level of English. Advocates in particular should be confident public speakers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the challenging nature and limited places for this committee we ask delegates to apply for a role in the ICJ, by &lt;strong&gt;submitting a letter of motivation&lt;/strong&gt; which explains:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Their previous MUN experiences&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- What makes them interested and qualified for the role&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delegates should also state which role they prefer (&lt;em&gt;judge or advocate&lt;/em&gt;) and if they are open to taking the &lt;em&gt;alternative&lt;/em&gt; if they aren’t accepted for their first choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Send &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;letters of application&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;any questions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; about the ICJ to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;elenir@islyon.org&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[about]]></title><description><![CDATA[In 2015, the UN adopted the Sustainable Development Goals, and set targets for 2030. Our conference will focus on Goal 6, Clean water and…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/about/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;In 2015, the UN adopted the Sustainable Development Goals, and set targets for 2030. Our conference will focus on Goal 6, Clean water and sanitation, and Goal 14, Life below water. The importance of these two goals is unparalleled. As the UN states, “Water is at the core of sustainable development and is critical for socio-economic development, energy and food production, healthy ecosystems and for human survival itself.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the past few years, the UN has called great attention to issues of water and now states that water is key to securing peace and a sustainable future. Goals 6 and 14 address issues of water scarcity, water security and equal access to water. They also focus on the protection of the earth’s essential water resources. These resources have been exploited as a source of power and economic profit, critically jeopardising the health of our oceans, lakes and rivers as well as coastal life. In addition, it is crucial to address the increasing conflicts, ranging from water access to maritime boundaries, which are continually shaping relations between nations. Finally, in a time of great technological surge, various solutions to counter water issues must be considered. Indeed, water issues bear upon all areas of human development and thus impact all of us as well as the health of the earth itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is our hope that in debating issues regarding ocean health, water scarcity and health the delegates of ILYMUN 2020 will draft these much-needed policies and reforms.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Contact]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/contact/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/contact/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[No title]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/countdown/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/countdown/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[By Students for Students]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/parallax/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/parallax/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Press]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/press/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/press/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Our Team]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/team/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/team/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why ILYMUN?]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/values/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/values/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ILYMUN 2020]]></title><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/hero/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/home-page/hero/</guid><pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>